<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Prince Music App</string>

    <!--    ALERT AND INPUT ERRORS  -->
    <string name="alert_default_positive_btn">OK</string>
    <string name="alert_default_negative_btn">Abbrechen</string>

    <!--    NETWORK ERROR   -->
    <string name="client_error_title">@string/unknown_error_title</string>
    <string name="client_error_desc">@string/unknown_error_desc</string>
    <string name="network_error_title">Keine Internetverbindung</string>
    <string name="network_error_desc">Bitte überprüfe Deine Datenverbindung in den Einstellungen und stelle sicher, dass Dein Gerät mit dem Internet verbunden ist.</string>
    <string name="not_found_error_title">Unbekannte Aktion</string>
    <string name="not_found_error_desc">Die Ausführung der Aktion ist im Moment nicht möglich.</string>
    <string name="server_error_title">@string/unknown_error_title</string>
    <string name="server_error_desc">@string/unknown_error_desc</string>
    <string name="unknown_error_title">Unbekannter Fehler</string>
    <string name="unknown_error_desc">Es ist ein unbekannter Fehler aufgetreten.</string>

    <string name="master_toolbar_title">%1$s (%2$d)</string>
    <string name="releases">Veröffentlichungen</string>

    <!--    Artist Detail Screen    -->
    <string name="artist_real_name">Bürgerlicher Name</string>
    <string name="artist_profile">Profil</string>
    <string name="artist_urls">Links</string>
    <string name="artist_name_variations">Varianten</string>
    <string name="artist_about">American singer, musician, songwriter, composer, arranger, sound engineer, producer, actor, dancer.
        Frontman of Prince And The Revolution (from 1984 to 1986).
        And from 1991 onwards he was Leader of the New Power Generation (which evolved the line-up almost every year) until his passing in 2016.
        Prince was inducted into the Rock And Roll Hall of Fame in 2004.
        \n\nBorn: 7 June 1958 in Minneapolis, Minnesota, USA.
        \nDied: 21 April 2016 in Chanhassen, Minnesota, USA.
        \n\nFrom 1986 to 1994 he ran Paisley Park and subsequently NPG Records resulting from his high profile disputes with Warner Bros. Records.
        Prince also had distribution of his music via various websites like NPG Music Club, lotusflow3r.com, 3rdeyegirl.com, and 3rdeyetunes.com.
        He was also supporter of Tidal (3), with exclusives being made available on the platform sporadically.
        \n\nSon of pianist and songwriter John L. Nelson, brother of Tyka Nelson (sister) &amp; Sharon Nelson (half-sister) was famous additionally for his work in the band Prince And The Revolution.
        \n\nPrince was married to Mayte (from 1996 to 2000) and to Manuela Testolini (from 2001 to 2006).
        He owned Paisley Park Studios where he spent so much time that it can be said that he lived in it, the doves Divinity And Majesty were his fellow residents."
    </string>

    <plurals name="videos">
        <item quantity="one">Video</item>
        <item quantity="other">Videos</item>
    </plurals>

</resources>